RON GUGLIELMONE

AUDIO AND ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING

310 694 7785

RonnieDayMusic@gmail.com

Profile

My areas of expertise include audio production, electronics, digital signal processing, computer programming, quantitative analysis, and web design. Seeking full-time employment in product management, software engineering, or finance.

Skills

Software and Programming Languages

Samples of my code can be seen at github.com/RonCanCode.

Languages	C, C++, Java, Javascript, CSS, HTML, SQL, MATLAB, Verilog, Faust.
Frameworks	JUCE, openFrameworks, Max, VST, STK.
Software	ProTools, Logic, Cubase, Reaper, Final Cut, EAGLE, LTSpice, ModelSim, Adobe CS, Office.

Audio Production

- Fifteen years of experience working with both digital and analog audio.
- Classically trained in music theory and composition.

Hardware Prototyping

- Understanding of circuit analysis and digital design paradigms.
- Proficient writing Verilog modules, test-benches, and synthesizing to FPGAs.
- Experience bead-boarding analog circuits, soldering, and characterizing devices.

Quantitative Analysis

- Comfortable applying mathematics to gain insight and solve problems.

Experience

Stanford Center for Professional Development

2015 - 2017

Control Room Operator

Simplify Studios

2009 - 2014

Owner

Sony Music Entertainment

2005 - 2007

Songwriter and Recording Artist

Education

Stanford University

2014 - 2017

BS, Electrical Engineering (expected in June)

Coursework in Multi-variable Calculus, Linear Algebra, Ordinary Differentials, Discrete Math, Digital Signal Processing, Probability, Computer Programming, Circuit Analysis, Digital Logic Design, Physics, Analog Communications, and Music.